This human may have been scared for her life, but we can take her word alone.
Let me borrow five soldiers, and I'll go see what's happening at City Hall, just in case.
That's not a bad idea. We'll regroup when you're done.
That story protected you. Maybe you were his comrade.
No. You probably just used him like all the others do.
Okay, follow me. Let's see what's going on at City Hall.
I'm coming, old friend.
Is there something wrong?
No. It's just getting really cloudy.
It's the perfect weather to launch an attack.
Yeah. Let's...
I'll see you next time.
Well, the vampires are definitely planning to ambush us.
I'll have to reconsider what we should do next.
What are you talking about?
I mean, we're gonna go and rescue them, aren't we?
So you're suggesting we walk head-on into something we know is a trap?
Yeah, if we have to.
Everyone shut up.
Okay.
We'll snipe and see how they react, just to test the waters.
There are three targets inside.
Powerful nobles named Crowley Eusford, Chess Bell, and Horned Skulled.
If it looks like our enemies are too strong for us to defeat, we'll leave the hostages.
What? Give up?
There's no way I'm leaving them hanging there like that.
Hey, you've gotta calm down.
Lieutenant Colonel, what do you believe is our top priority at this point in the mission?
We can't afford to lose any more troops, especially elites like you.
That makes freeing the hostages a secondary concern.
Moving forward, I'm gonna need all of you.
What you're saying is, this isn't over.
We have to survive because there's another mission waiting after this one, right?
Well, that's one way to look at it.
We need to keep the vampires in Nagaya.
Doing so lets our main unit in Shibuya move undetected.
That's one of the primary reasons we're here.
Wait, so the Shibuya team is on the move right now?
Yeah. If things are going as planned, they should be on their way to Shinjuku.
So basically, what he's saying is that this whole attack on Nagaya was nothing but a decoy.
Not exactly.
The extermination of the nobles will have a huge impact on the war.
But from now on, our mission is to keep the enemy distracted as long as we possibly can.
Which is why...
We're gonna see how they react to a little expert snipey.
If they attack in force, we'll run.
But if we see an opening, we'll try to save all of the hostages.
Best-case scenario, we'll kill the nobles too.
Now you're dreaming. Things never go that well.
Why are you always such a pessimist?
Come on, Curran, I'm just telling it like it is.
Don't worry, I'm still gonna kill these guys.
Pick a sniping perch, Yoichi.
Let's show everyone what you've learned.
Right.
Look alive and get into position.
Be ready for a swift counterattack.
Roger that.
We're prepared, right?
Yeah.
Okay, I've got the fourth floor.
Focus your attention on the windows in the next level up.
Got it.
Hey, I've got a visual on a vampire.
It's a noble.
His back's to me.
I don't think he's noticed us yet.
Then take the damn shot.
Now!
Fly true for me, Gekko-een.
What is this thing?
How strange.
Sir, I failed to hit my target.
Ordinarily, even a noble wouldn't have been able to dodge a shot like that.
Which means...
That this guy must be an extremely powerful vampire.
It's no wonder nine of our strongest teams couldn't handle him.
We don't stand a chance.
He's right.
I recognize this guy.
We faced him before.
Huh?
He's the vampire we fought when we were headed to Shinjuku.
And his comrades are with him.
Huh?
Hey, give me that!
Are you okay, Lord Crowley?
What was that weird thing?
Some kind of exploding bird?
It would appear that we have some visitors.
Yoichi's right.
That guy is big trouble.
He's like insanely strong.
I see.
Then I highly doubt we could beat him by force alone.
So then, what?
We've got two choices.
We can shoot our comrades now before they're tortured.
And then get the hell out of this town.
You can't be serious!
Hey, don't freak out yet!
That's one way, but what's the other option?
We somehow managed to split up the nobles, then save the hostages and retreat.
Naturally, that plan's more dangerous.
I doubt we'd all survive.
We're not leaving our comrades behind, right?
Gorin?
I think the smartest move is to kill the hostages and run.
They didn't attack us after Yoichi's failed shot.
So we're not important to them.
We should retreat while we're still able to.
You bastard!
Don't be stupid!
You're the one who's acting stupid!
I've got close friends in that group of hostages.
It's killing me to even think of leaving them behind.
But you don't see me making a scene like a spoiled brat.
But, Lieutenant Colonel, this is still a decoy mission, isn't it?
If we leave the nobles alone, aren't we putting the Shibuya unit at risk?
Yes.
Well, in that case...
Yeah, I know.
There's no way around it.
We have to attack.
We'll put on a big show so they think we're the main unit.
I'm not against killing the bloodsuckers.
But I don't see how we stand a chance with them waiting around for us like this.
If they start to overwhelm us, we'll retreat.
Come on.
We should move locations.
How odd.
There's no second wave.
We could have some fun and go hunt them down ourselves.
I would bet that's exactly what our enemies are hoping for.
We'll be patient and let them come to us.
They must have realized that they didn't stand a chance against us after their first attack failed.
Maybe they just got scared and ran away.
Humans have a bad habit of making stupid decisions,
especially when the smart choice is against their orders.
Huh?
Wait, what do you mean, Lord Crowley?
They've been commanded to destroy us, so there's little chance they're going to back out now.
They're loyal even in the face of certain death.
Or there's something else.
It's possible they have a hidden agenda.
Farid's going to want to know everything about this attack.
We should gather as much intel as possible.
I don't like Lord Farid.
He's always trying to seem so mysterious.
It's annoying.
You know, Chess, for once I actually agree with you.
He can be a little much.
But you have to admit, when he's around, there's never a dull moment.
All right, ladies.
Here's our new plan of attack.
We capture the commander, since he's the one who will have the most info.
Got it?
Yes.
Pay attention.
Here's the new plan.
Shinya and the rest of my team will attack Crowley, Usford, and his comrades.
Shinya and Narumi's teams will attempt to rescue the hostages while we're fighting.
Do you think you'll be all right with just you guys?
Our basic strategy will be to strike and run away.
We should be able to hold them off for a bit.
That's only going to give you five minutes to rescue all the hostages you can.
After that, we have to retreat and join the other teams at the Nagaya airport at once.
Where are we going after we get to the airport?
There should be a transport helicopter waiting for us there, along with new directives.
We'll follow those orders.
We attack in seven minutes.
Everyone, take your positions.
Yes, sir.
How does it look, Shinya?
Our enemies aren't making any moves.
But then, they're most likely waiting on us.
Who knows what's inside, though?
We're walking into this partially blind.
Lieutenant Colonel, are we really attacking them first?
Yeah.
With Ghoshy's illusionary spell, he can make it look like 200 men are fighting alongside of us.
Isn't that right?
Sure, but there's one big problem with your plan.
I'd have to get dangerously close to our enemies.
Then why are you still standing here?
What?
Sounds like Ghoshy's our first casualty.
Geez, thanks for the vote of confidence.
Should we do this together?
No.
If we're going to free as many of them as we can in five minutes.
Then we should go separately.
Okay.
Good luck to you.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah.
And one more thing, noobs.
Don't you dare die.
Same goes for you guys.
Oh, I'm not concerned about my squad surviving this.
Not when they've got an incredible team leader like me.
That's all.
Let's move.
We've got comrades to save.
Roger that.
We should move to our positions, too.
Yeah.
All right.
There's no use putting this off.
If you have any last words, now's your chance.
We're ready.
You can count on us.
Okay.
Okay, everyone.
Let's synchronize our clocks.
Please set an alarm for exactly five minutes.
When it goes off, we have to retreat no matter what's happening at the time.
Do you understand?
This is an order.
When our time is up, we leave the battlefield no matter how many people we've saved.
That's the only rule for this mission.
It can't be broken.
That means, even if we have to leave someone behind, we retreat.
But...
No buts, Yu.
I'm the team leader here.
We can only get out of this.
But disobeying puts us all at risk.
So please...
Please follow my orders.
Be a good soldier.
I will.
It's a simple job.
All we have to do is save everyone.
I don't think you get how hard this is going to be.
No.
I think this is going to work out.
Our teamwork has gotten a lot better, too.
Hmm.
And on top of that, we've all become really good friends.
That might be an exaggeration.
Hey.
Why are you so mean?
I'm just kidding.
It's time to move out.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Lieutenant Colonel, what are you doing here?
They're too powerful.
You've got to get out of here. Just go on without us.
Go get them.
Damn, my cock.
All right, do it, Ghoshy.
Behold the Demon Army's best men. Let's do this.
Attack!
Don't let them into the building!
Are they just going to leave us all hanging here?
Are you okay?
Narumi, what's going on?
Kageyama, Yayoi, Rika.
Get the other members of Kado's team free.
Shusaku, you're coming with me.
There we go.
Things are finally getting interesting.
Huh. I've seen that face before.
You must be leading this hopeless assault.
I'm here to destroy you, blood sucker!
It looks like you're pretty strong.
But that's not enough!
What about you, Commander?
Rookie mistake.
Not watching your back.
Well, I guess this is checkmate.
Lieutenant Colonel Curran!
Leave it to them.
If we step in and try to help out,
we'll only end up getting in the way.
We have to!
I've got a better idea.
What are your orders?
Continue the mission as planned.
Move fast and save as many of the troops as you can.
Shinoah, should we try and help them?
Are we just going to let Goran die?
Let's get up there and take out some nobles!
Not a bad idea.
You might be able to launch some kind of pincer attack.
Yeah, Shinoah.
Let's do it.
Okay.
We've got three minutes.
Plenty of time to save the day.
Let's go!
I'll come up with a plan on the way.
Please promise that you'll do as I say.
Oh, that guy's going to be a problem.
He's on a totally different level than the other nobles.
I'm afraid this might be it for us.
No way.
Things are all going as I planned.
Who are you trying to kid, Goran?
At least we did a solid job of getting their attention.
You and I make pretty good bait.
You done rusting?
Because I'd kind of like to escape now.
You can't leave.
The fun's just getting started.
It'd be a shame for you two to miss the main event.
I insist you stay.
I can't allow you to disappoint Lord Grohler.
Why can't we just start the show already?
I'm feeling thirsty.
I don't want to be rude.
Then I guess we have to stay here and keep the three of them entertained.
Why are you going that way?
Goran and Shinya are on the fourth floor.
Just stay quiet and follow my lead.
You murdered.
Lord Grohler, shall we join this dance?
Don't worry.
I can handle these two on my own.
You shouldn't take your rice off of me!
You're finally starting to put up a real fight.
Why are you going to put up a real fight?
Now!
This is going to get boring if you keep repeating that same move.
Oh.
It appears that they've escaped.
So how badly are you wounded, Shinya?
It could be worse.
I could have broken all my bones.
If you're strong enough to choke, then walk on your own.
You're not getting rid of me that easily.
This way I can hold them off behind us.
Hey!
Why are you running away?
To be honest, I've never really liked running.
You could always stop chasing us!
You guys attacked us first, and now you don't want us coming after you?
I'm always amazed at how selfish humans can be.
Are they coming?
No.
Maybe I managed to scare the bastards off with that last shot.
Shinya!
Gurren!
Oops, I forgot I'm not supposed to kill you.
At least not until after you've answered all of my questions.
Damn it.
I'm already dead, Shinya.
You need to take command and finish the mission without me.
That's an order, Shinya.
You should listen to your commander.
Before I decide, I need two subjects for intel.
Ah!
Next time on Seraph of the End
Demon's Lullaby